Thank you.
Grenade!
pay one's respects by bowing with hands in front of one's chest
I'm sorry. The elevator's broken. Bye-bye.
Don't move.
Over there. Come on, over there.
What are you still doing?
I'll tune your engine. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Now you've got a great car. It's faster than a rocket.
Your father didn't ask me to take care of you when he died.
I'd have thrown you overboard, you idiot.
know
What's next?
The plane. What?
The yacht. What?
No, it's kite flying.
Go on.
Kite flying Kite flying
pay one's respects by bowing with hands in front of one's chest
Romano, it's so good to see you again.
Manti, welcome back.
Mantis, have a good time in Hong Kong?
No, the godfather's not happy about it.
Me too.
He's waiting to see you. You be careful.
Thank you. Thank you.
The Godfather of Anthony
Go play with your mommy, little cutie.
Manti, my boy.
I'm sorry, dear Godfather.
You're sorry. What the hell are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
But... this man...
Every time you make a mistake, you always have an explanation.
Now tell me who did it.
white glove
It's him. There he is.
He's in Venice.
I always trusted you, son.
I've always been faithful to you, too, Godfather.
Anyway, go to Hong Kong and get the diamond back to me
Why me?
Otherwise, you'll be a dead fish.
You can use my connections in Hong Kong.
I can lose the diamonds, but not the heart and face of an Italian.
You know what?
But I'm British.
Idiot, you haven't figured out that the English are related to the
Italians.
How come I've never heard of it?
The diamond or your life.
Morning, Commissioner. According to our information.
slow
You don't have to talk nonsense to foreigners
It's okay to speak in person, Hana.
A serious robbery took place recently in Tsim Sha Tsui Centre
A valuable shipment of diamonds was taken and no one reported the robbery.
Let's look at the information we have collected
He's a local gangster, Szeto Buren, who collects stolen goods.
This is the new kid on the international smuggling block.
He's Italian. His name is Montisutto.
Stuart had nothing to lose in this robbery.
And this Italian guy didn't report it.
The only clue left at the scene was a white glove.
As for our further information, it's a blank.
The source of the above information is an undercover agent from us.
We can't release his name because he's in a special position.
It's a marginalized person.
Don't make any noise. Don't ruin the atmosphere here.
This is the world's most famous thief. He's called the White Glove.
Specialized robbery of diamond gold
He has seven passports, eight names.
Nine identities and two genders.
He's here on a case.
You could say it's our pleasure.
It's our misfortune, too.
So we have to find a way to get his nemesis to do it.
The archrival
That's right. He's got two nemeses.
The first one is the Pink Panther, Petersler.
Unfortunately, he's already gone to heaven.
The second one is...
Don't block the view.
America's Bald Detective
He's been demoted from a bureau chief to a toilet warden to catch a white
glove.
From black hair to bald while his boss ordered him
No more white gloves in three months.
He'll have to adopt early and go back to his hometown to eat his rice.
So we decided to invite the bald detective to Hong Kong
Because he's the most enthusiastic white glove catcher.
And this year's most outstanding young man, Superintendent Ho Tung-sze.
That man-child.
We're sending her to help Detective Baldy on this case.
Yeah, that's great.
Brother, is there any fire?
It's a lady
The lady must have fire all over her.
But... you're too conservative.
A conservative girl is a prude.
You want to see it?
Yeah, you don't need to tell me that.
Don't blink.
Which? Fire, fire, fire.
You piss me off, this gun will go off any minute.
It's his fault. It's not my fault. We won't do it again.
Let's go. It's all your fault.
Let's not talk about it. Let's go.
What are you looking at? I've never seen a woman's thighs before.
I'm just looking at your gunny sack.
Officer Ho, you're here to pick up Detective Bald's plane.
I don't have time to pick him up. I'm here for the next guy.
There are so many people. How will you find them?
Don't worry, he'll show up as soon as I yell.
The Edge
It's not here.
Don't run away.
I can't help it.
You're still running.
Don't run.
Come down.
There's no one there. You're still trying to beat me up.
I'm just covering for you. What's the news?
There are three. Two are real and one is fake.
Well, let's tell you two real things.
It's really the bald American detective coming to Hong Kong today
Your superiors sent you to help him with his investigation.
You know our top secret.
How else could I be an informant?
And?
And that's the day someone tried to rob the Chow Tai Fook gold shop
How did you know it was today?
The day I chose for him.
Is this a good day?
It's because it's not a good day.
It's fake.
False is when your superiors say you won't pick up the plane at the airport.
Just let me come around here for a bit.
I'm so unlucky to meet a man-child like you.
It's time.
We should be here. We're not waiting. I'm going to check the case.
What case?
It's none of your business. It's a big case anyway.
Clouds against water Snow against wind
Whiteboard vs. Red, Big Four.
Young man, you're so unlucky.
Self-touch is the best
My name is Chan Pak Keung
My name is Oui Keung.
My name is a fake.
Mine's fake too.
Boss, someone's coming to rob us later.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Don't move. What are you doing? Climbing down.
Get in the corner. Come on.
Fill this bag up. Come on.
Attention all units, Chow Tai Fook gold shop alarm has been sounded.
Go see what's going on.
Where is Chow Tai Fook Gold Shop
One turn and we're there.
Go see.
Brother, the bag is full.
Okay, get out and get a car. Don't move.
Don't move.
Don't move. Sit back down or you'll break your head.
Brother, the car is ready.
Don't move!
Drive.
Get out of the car. The police are commandeering your car.
Key!
Here.
Come on, hurry up, baldy.
It's hard to go slow, but it's too easy to go fast.
Hurry up!
You want to die? How do you drive? Drive carefully. Come on.
You old man, you want us dead.
Accident. Sorry.
Come on, drive! Come on!
Bastard! You hit and run!
Get out of the car, police.
One of our own. I was a police officer in the States.
You're a police officer. You're a rustic.
Smuggled in from the mainland
not
They're all over the street. They have all the stuff they need in the toy
stores.
I caught a bunch of thieves for you. Take a look.
Come in.
Get out of the way. Sit down.
You four, who's the boss?
He's the boss.
Buffalo, monkey, confession.
Get up.
Baldy, come with me.
Get out of the way.
sit
Okay, thanks.
That way.
Okay, okay, okay.
You won't be able to kick it.
Baldy, are you familiar with the laws here?
I'm not familiar with the laws here. I know American law by heart.
How dare you rob in here? When did you get here?
Just arrived.
How did you smuggle yourself in?
I came by plane.
Do you have any relatives or friends?
I don't have any relatives, and I don't have any friends that I know.
There's one who knows me.
Who
Hong Kong Governor
He called me and asked me to come.
How dare you be a smartass?
You can't answer my fucking question if I ask you now.
If you want to answer
It can be used as testimony in court in the future, right?
What's the name?
My name is AlbertAu.
English names are also popular on the mainland, where they're from.
Taipei
Not married.
No. And you?
What's it to you, gender?
I have a moustache.
So what if you have a moustache?
A beard is a man.
I'm not like you. I don't have the brains of a man or the body of a woman.
What gender are you, male or female?
You want to have an affair?
I don't hit you. You hit me.
Don't move.
That's great. That's great. That's fantastic.
The bald detective really lives up to his name.
There, this man-child is the real deal.
Superintendent Ho is really something. He's working more efficiently.
But... it's just a little slow.
I've arranged for Superintendent Ho to help you with this case.
She... Forget it.
To protect your identity, I arranged for you to be a married couple.
What? He's my husband.
He's not worthy of being my husband. Look at his dead face.
That's what I said, fatty. Have you booked the hotel yet?
I've ordered it.
Put her in the room next to mine. Get her a room too. I want to be
married to her.
You're beautiful.
What about Superintendent Ho? Are you afraid of him?
What am I afraid of? I'm not used to hotels. Come and stay at my place if
you dare.
Go to your house.
You're afraid.
I'm afraid. I'm afraid she'll eat me.
Don't treat me like a woman, baldy.
The whole police department treats me like a man.
We're just pretending to be husband and wife. Don't take it seriously.
What are you afraid of? It's not like we haven't seen it before. Come on
out.
According to the information my informant gave me.
This is the kid who took the diamonds. His name is King Kong.
Nicknamed the Flying Thief.
He also has a partner called Fountain of Mouth.
He's the Fountain of Mouth. He's a self-proclaimed son-of-a-bitch.
All over the woman's phone
They haven't been seen since they did the case.
King Kong lives on the fifth floor across the street.
King Kong, I'm a fountain of water.
Calling my name again.
No, red cats are called black cats, over.
The black cat heard you. Tell me.
Report the black cat. I'm gonna put the diamond in my collection. - No.
Also mentions Diamond
It's peanuts. I'm going to tell you where I collected the bag of peanuts.
You can't tell me. I'll talk in my sleep.
I know. If I don't tell you this time, something will happen.
Why?
It's because I've recently picked up the sister of a maniac.
You dare to pick up Madman's sister? This time you're dead.
That's why I'm telling you. Let's find a restaurant and talk.
All right, that one.
No, I can't tell you.
If you don't tell me, how do I know which one?
Okay, I'll tell you in a whisper, you listen carefully.
I can't hear you. Speak up.
That's stupid. Seventh Heaven Western Restaurant. Did you hear that?
Go to the Seventh Heaven Western Restaurant. The Black Cat is waiting for
you.
You've picked up Madman's girl. Give the diamond to Black Cat.
Remember, it's not a diamond. It's a peanut.
It's him.
It's the white glove. Go after him.
vajra
tomboy
Don't go, King Kong.
Not that one. This one.
You want me dead.
You can't do that.
You bastard!
pay one's respects by bowing with hands in front of one's chest
Don't fucking run. I'm gonna get you.
Don't go, King Kong.
Stop the car. Stop the car.
Man-child. Bye-bye.
pay one's respects by bowing with hands in front of one's chest
parking
Sir, a few people, please.
I'll do it myself.
The red cat is here.
The bag of diamonds. No, it's peanuts.
The bag of peanuts. I hid it safely.
I've carved this secret into two separate women.
Go ahead. Why are you so nervous?
It's the one in the movies where they tell secrets to other people.
They must have killed him before he got halfway through.
Don't be afraid. The one you're listening to won't die.
Come on.
The bag of diamonds.
What's up?
I got shot. Didn't you see that?
They're just opening champagne. Say it.
I don't think it's safe here. Go to the toilet.
All right, you can talk now.
Let's talk about it.
I put the bag of diamonds
No, I hid the peanuts in Kowloon.
Wait, I can't talk.
What's going on?
Don't worry, you can talk all you want. I'm deaf. I can't hear anything.
He's a mute. He didn't say anything. Let's go.
What's up?
madman
I'm gonna die this time.
Let's slip out the back door.
Come in.
There's no one here. Go ahead and talk.
The bag of peanuts is hidden in Wait a minute, did you notice that this
elevator is very narrow?
Watch your right. Sorry. Excuse me.
Could you move over, please?
Don't be afraid. It's a foreign devil.
You're the one who's a ghost
Yeah.
It's okay, we just have to say that the Shaolin monk shaved his head and
became a monk.
Burning Red Lotus Temple. Mystery on the line.
What is it?
It means repeating each word more than once.
Then you should speak up.
That packet of peanuts is hidden in Dragon 9
What did you say?
The bag of peanuts is hidden in Kowloon.
Please, let's open it for a second.
Get out of the way.
Even the kids can talk about it. What's the mystery?
There's no one here.
Wait. Let's get out.
That way.
Black cat, I'm here. I'm afraid of heights. My arms and legs are weak now.
But you remember, Rose.
What rose? Let's not talk about that. What are you doing now?
What can I do? Can't you see what I'm doing?
I'm not in the middle of anything, but I'm really sorry.
What's wrong with me?
I'm sorry that you can't eat the peanuts
It's okay, Red Cat. You remember.
No matter what, we'll always be best buddies.
Always.
I got the white glove.
This is not a white glove.
The white gloves are the ones with the hooked nose and blue eyes, Ahjumma.
I guarantee he's the thief who robbed the diamond, Uncle.
He doesn't look like a thief.
unlike
There's a way. Let me try it and he'll know.
How do I try?
Just use my science certificate from Scotland Yard in the States.
But you want to work with me.
Please sit down.
No need to check. Sit down. Sit down.
I won't answer any questions until my lawyer gets here.
Let's play an IQ game.
I'll wait until my lawyer gets here.
Do you know who I am?
I haven't asked for advice yet.
I'm the bald Chinese detective who came in first place in Scotland Yard.
You've heard of me.
Heard of it. Heard of it.
We work together
I'll wait until my lawyer gets here.
son of a bitch
Give me your hand.
It's not that I don't give you face.
What? It's not in there yet.
Don't mess around
Bring it.
Did you hear that?
Detective, let's play the game.
Okay, I'll play a reaction game with you.
You take your hand out and each of you hit it.
Whoever can hit the other guy wins.
So who's gonna do it first?
Of course it's me. Show me your hands.
That way.
It's my turn, right?
Can we not play?
Get your hands out.
Which hand is it?
This one.
Decision made.
My lawyer's here.
Now it's my turn.
You son of a bitch.
Where's my gun?
Here.
It's not mine.
She has yours.
Have you had enough?
There's another one. This is the one I grew up with. I'm gonna win.
What if we don't win?
Let you go.
Come here. Come here.
It's simple. Hold the ear in your right hand.
Press your left hand to the ground and turn five times.
Then go get the poker cards. You win if you get them.
If you don't get it, you'll have to work with me.
No problem. You show me.
It's easy. It's like a child singing. Hold your ear and press down.
Heads down, butts up. First lap of the Chrysanthemum Garden, second lap
of the Dragon Boat.
My back is sore on the third lap, and I'm out of breath on the fourth.
The fifth circle is weak. Do you get it?
Got it. Come on.
Come on.
Which side should I turn first?
Stupid. Just follow me around. See?
It's so slow.
It's okay if it's fast. I'm moving you. Is it fast?
How can you make five turns so fast?
Sure, I'm on my third, fourth, fifth, right?
I see. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
First lap Chrysanthemum Garden Second lap Dragon Boat Watch
My back is sore on the third lap, and I'm out of breath on the fourth.
Fifth lap, legs are weak. Sixth lap, gold stars.
Thank you for your hard work.
pay one's respects by bowing with hands in front of one's chest
I used to be able to go five rounds without losing my face.
He's gone. What for?
I'm gonna take a break.
I'm a white glove. I'm gonna kill you.
If you want to kill me, you have to wait a while
Why?
Because someone rang the doorbell, idiot.
Jao, boss.
Come on.
Kid, don't go. I'll go get help.
call for help
It's him. It's him. Go after him.
Call the Superintendent. He's got the door up.
Okay, second walk.
know
Police station? Someone hit my door.
You got the wrong number. I'm a white glove.
I have a gift for you.
Hurry up and check the door.
What is this thing?
This is exactly the same as a diamond robbery.
Chan Pak Keung, it's your turn.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
I can't get it out.
Hold it out straight.
Yes.
Slotted. Look behind you.
If it wasn't for me, you'd be dead.
Thank you for saving my life.
How will you repay me?
We'll talk when my lawyer gets here.
Detective, you're gonna have to get me up here first.
I'm working on the diamond case.
I didn't do it.
Then I've come to the wrong person.
I admit it. I admit it. I did it.
What about the bag of diamonds?
I don't know.
If you don't tell me, my hands will get weak.
Don't get soft. I told you.
The bag of diamonds is over there.
The red cat is hiding.
Where's Red Cat? He's dead.
Again, lie to me.
All right, I promise to help you find the bag of diamonds.
And you're gonna help me catch the white glove after I get the diamond
back.
Okay, but you have to promise me one thing.
What's up?
You can't sue me afterwards.
I promise you won't be guilty.
What's your guarantee?
I swear.
The bombs are ready.
We're ready.
Take it up.
Where's the wiretap?
Installed above
Who are you sending up?
Loud Public
He even makes a noise when he breathes.
Don't worry, he won't make a sound this time.
There's no way I'm staying in this place for another minute.
How do you think we're going to live in a dull place?
Eat up before you curse.
Eat. Look what these steaks look like.
Lack of color and flavor.
You son of a bitch.
And you, bald guy, uncultured and disgusting.
And he wants me to share a room with him.
And the air here is filthy, lacking in oxygen, it's suffocating.
Look, he doesn't even make a sound.
What about the bomb?
I've already taken it up.
Even the doorbell is so hard to hear
What's up?
Give me shoes.
It must be my sister's. Put it down.
Put it down. Okay.
I can't stand it here anymore. I'm going home.
If you want to work with me, come to my house
Hello.
I live here.
Me too.
Sister, you're back.
Don't you look at him. He's a pornographer. Get in.
Sister, who are these two people?
I'll introduce you to this one. You don't need to know this one.
This is useless even if you know it. Sit down.
Have a seat.
Didn't you say you were going back?
Yeah, let's go. Let's go.
It's okay. Sit down for a while and then go back.
Sis, Japan is really fun.
Have you ever been to Japan?
I've been there.
do business
No, a thief.
Shh. Didn't you see that? The kid saw your sister.
It's like he's been possessed. Now he's forgotten his father's name.
What's your father's last name?
I don't know.
Did you rob the diamond?
It was me who grabbed it.
Where is it hidden?
It's the Red Cat's hideout.
How can I find it?
He carved the secret into two girls.
How do I find those two girls?
With you, I don't have to go looking for those two girls anymore, you
bastard.
Baldy, did you hear that?
I told you this kid stole these diamonds.
Did you lie to me?
How could I lie to you?
I'd rather lie to that bald guy and that man-child than to you.
Why are you holding my hand?
We're all men. What does it matter?
You heard him. He's the only one who knows where the diamonds are.
I'm ordering you now, before he finds the diamond.
You have to keep him safe and sound.
Chang has taken the bombs up.
What? Where's Chang?
(located) at
Come on, get up there and get the bomb back.
No, we're out of time.
Why?
Enough time to go up, not enough time to come down.
I don't care. We can't blow him up no matter what.
You're not leaving yet.
I'll go. Look.
The air is better here.
The bald guy's head is a bit more shiny
And these steaks are better.
But your sister is a little mean.
What did you say?
A little bit. A little bit.
Even the sound of the doorbell sounds better
I'll open the door more quickly.
Wrong delivery
It's stupid to send the wrong one.
This shoe box is a little heavy.
Please walk faster.
Boss, be careful.
run fast
Woman's name and phone number on Mouthwatering Springs
It's all the work of this tattoo expert.
I hope he'll remember.
Cock-eye, do me a favor. Think again for me.
What's been carved into the fountain of mouth lately?
It's either a woman's name or a phone number.
He's covered in it. I remember that.
Has he brought any girls to get tattooed lately?
Yes, two.
That's ridiculous. He told me to carve letters into the asses of those
two girls.
You must remember what was carved there.
If everyone remembers, I'll have to install a computer here.
Good. Now there are fewer clues.
Less chance of finding diamonds again.
Your chances of going to jail are a little closer.
You're in a bit of a hurry. There's still some thread, but it's a little
harder.
What do you mean?
As Izumi was dying, he shouted "Rose!
I suspect he may have a girlfriend named Rose.
sir
Did you two just get out of the tattoo parlor?
be
Then it's time to take a picture at my place.
Why?
Because everyone who gets a tattoo likes to come to my photo booth for
pictures.
Can't get to the mouth of the water spring he
Don't be embarrassed. This is the one.
rose
Madam, we're not here to take pictures.
Why don't you take a picture? To fish in the water?
Come on, let's go.
We're trying to get a picture for a friend.
Who is it?
Has anyone taken any nude pictures here lately?
Rowan
So you're friends of Rowan's.
No, we're friends from Fountain of Mouth.
Who are you talking about?
The girl's phone number is engraved all over.
I can't talk, I can't talk, I can't talk, I can't talk.
I see. Red cat, right?
That's right.
That poor guy dropped two bucks and disappeared.
Those pictures are very important to us.
No, I don't know where they put it.
I'm busy here. Let's go.
Give me a hand.
Let me do it. You watch the door and tell me when someone comes.
You're in trouble.
What? Robbery?
No
I have a husband's
It's okay.
I'm very old.
Just right.
I'm not pretty.
I can settle.
What did you give me? It's a stocking
So she won't recognize my face.
Why don't you put one on, too, so she doesn't recognize you?
No.
Don't mess around. I'll just give you the photos.
high bar
Both of them are here.
I found out. The first girl works for this taxi company.
I'll deal with it alone later.
Why?
You can only deal with old ladies like that. This is a big girl.
Of course it's up to me.
That's not really true.
I was in the Most Attractive Man contest in Chinatown.
What happened?
Of course, I'm the winner.
How many people attended
I'm the only one.
Anyway, don't say anything later.
You know what, kid? I'm on the case. I'll take care of the girls.
Hello.
What are you doing, damn it? Don't waste your time. Let's go.
Who did you just say hello to?
Who spanked my ass and hit me on the head again?
Wait, you watch. I'll deal with the girl.
No, I have to say it.
I told you not to make a sound.
I have to say.
Shh. Shh what?
A traffic vehicle knocked down a traffic light at the entrance of the
Department of Transportation, causing traffic chaos.
Hello Taxi Service Desk
Got it!
Your wife asks if you're coming home for dinner.
Tell her I'm not going home for dinner. Mary, can I buy you dinner?
Come on, don't flatter yourself.
Miss Mary, how are you?
Who are you?
I'm an attorney from Mouthwatering Springs. This is his father, Uncle
Wong.
Hello!
I don't know where he died.
Even you curse him to death!
He's really dead, but we don't know where.
truly
Yeah, and he died a horrible death.
When he was dying, he was screaming your name.
He was dying and he called my name.
There's a lady. Her beloved Pekingese is missing.
Anyone who finds one, please notify the taxi desk.
Mr CHAN, this girl is really sympathetic
May God bless that Pekingese.
He still has a legacy to leave to you.
Legacy? How many?
There's half a million.
It's US dollars.
truly
The Pekinese dog has been found. Thank God. Thank you, Fountain of Water.
Father, Mizukuisen is a man of God.
Make yourselves at home. Don't be polite.
We need proof of your identity before we can complete the paperwork.
No problem. I have an ID card.
No, he wants to see your farts.
The features on her body.
This bastard told you all this.
How would he have seen it if I hadn't gotten drunk that night?
So you're drunk.
I got it. It's the fire department down the alley. There's a fire truck
outside.
And the coffin truck outside of the funeral home... hit a man.
Real trouble.
It's ridiculous that you guys want to see my ass.
Look at that. Half a million dollars.
Don't say I do. You do too.
Am I right?
So what if I don't show it to you?
The estate was automatically transferred to his father, Uncle Wong.
What proof do you have that he's his father?
I love my dad.
Where the hell are we going?
If you take a picture of yourself here, you won't be embarrassed.
No, it's embarrassing.
Half a million dollars.
I don't have any change.
I have it. Take it, please.
No peeking.
Okay, remember, it's not the front, it's the mark on the butt.
should
He's taking a student photo with his daughter
Go to Miss Hong Kong's
older brother
Sir, this photo is yours, and this case is yours.
pay one's respects by bowing with hands in front of one's chest
stand
Who are you two?
Brother CHAN Sing
Who is he?
He's the maniacal Hoshiro who killed Mizukuisen.
I don't know him. You can talk to him.
Who are you two again?
This time it was an accident.
I'm not ready yet.
Boy, that's not good.
Don't be afraid. We're two brothers. I'll be here when you die.
Who doesn't know that this site belongs to me, Madman?
How dare you trick my sister into taking nude photos?
Whose idea was it?
I think it's a dead end. Two people can still have a partner.
Admit everything together.
No problem.
Come on, which one of you had the idea?
The idea of two people
Who came up with this idea?
We came up with it together.
Who asked my sister to take a picture first?
Open your mouth together.
have a certain kind of
Both of them.
That's great.
Both are fine.
What do we do now?
It doesn't matter. You can admit it first.
Whose idea was it?
It's mine for now.
It's so hard.
Do you have a share?
Let's admit it, son.
He said to admit one thing first.
Don't worry, I'll replace you after two breaths.
It's my turn.
My nose isn't as big as yours. I'll have to suck on it a bit more.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm coming up.
It's so nice now. I really don't want to go back up there.
Okay, it's my turn. It's hard work.
You called me a nice one.
older brother
Brother is coming
I've fallen for it, brother. Let me down.
What's the hurry? The air is good up there
You little bastard, don't put me down yet. You want to hang me?
I can't. I'm dying. I'm dying.
So you're not dead yet.
You're dead and I'm still alive.
That's not what I said. How could you let me down?
Okay, it's my turn.
No, I need to breathe.
You're not righteous enough.
You're crazy, now you're talking about righteousness, gasping for breath
You hillbilly, you want me to admit first that it was all your idea.
So it was your idea.
That's right. That's right. Stab him a few more times.
Bastard, you have no sense of justice. You want to kill someone with a
knife.
Fatty, he's the one who asked your sister to take the picture.
What? No, it's not even Hoshi, it's Fatty Hoshi.
It's better for me to call him fat to his face than for you to call him a
bastard behind his back.
What?
Bastard wants to catch his breath. Now you're in trouble.
Don't worry, I know this place well. There's no train coming.
No train.
There's no train. You could be rolled over in four pieces. Come on.
What's the point of staying in a hospital for something so trivial?
And you have to specify this floor. This one.
Well, it's not good enough to let you rest.
If anything happens, just ring the bell and call me.
Yeah, that's not true.
You two treat me like I'm invisible.
I've got other patients to see.
I have a chance with Doraemon, but not you and the man-child.
I can't. I haven't had my fun yet.
That's nice. She's meaner than you.
Those two guys are in that room.
The man-child is here.
You're not leaving. Now you have to help me.
These two fucking bastards left me to go investigate the case by myself.
I'm gonna have to go after them.
What did you say?
How can you call Ho Tung Sze a man-child? She's my dream girl.
She may be mean, but she's made of women from head to toe.
How come you don't see the soft side of her?
I'm telling you, I'm after her now.
She's a divine woman.
When did she ever cross her arms in front of us?
She never yelled at me.
When she's standing.
You look like a lady.
When you're sitting, you look like a little girl. You don't cross your legs.
She's very gentle. You don't believe me. Ask her later when she comes in.
ALBERT
When did you get in?
I just got in. I just wanted to tell you.
Say it.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
I lost it.
What are you doing in here again?
I forgot to get my clothes.
older sister
What's wrong with my sister? I've never seen her like this before.
She's fine. You better get her checked out by a brain surgeon.
HELLO Man Woman Phone
Your sister's phone.
Doraemon, I can hear my phone outside.
Manny, I'm a marginalized person
You're a fucking marginal. I asked you to check on the maniacs, and now you're
calling me.
She can't change her nature.
And torture her a little.
What? To kill the bald detective?
You tell him.
If he touches the bald detective, I'll kill him.
And you, too. If you get in my way, I'm gonna cramp you up.
Madman said he'd kill you.
I got it. You go out.
Repair of toilets
It's fixed.
It's broken again.
Boss, OK.
Remote Control
Just press this button, and you're all goodbye.
God bless.
What the fuck are you doing hugging my sister?
Damn it, you're still holding me.
It's your wife's birthday tonight. You have to go back and spend time
with her.
And you?
How can I make a light bulb?
Tell me the truth.
I have a date with Doraemon
What's with all the darkness? Responding to energy conservation?
albert, look what a difference I made today.
You must have been sent by your superiors to work as an undercover agent for a
prostitute.
Take your feet off. The couch is dirty.
It's my birthday.
What about that?
Let's open the champagne first.
Who made this steak?
I made it myself.
First time in the kitchen
It's awful.
Is it your birthday? - Yes.
How old are you?
Thirty years old
A flower. Congratulations.
No, a man is a flower at 30, a woman is a crap at 30.
Why can't you get married at 30?
No one wants it.
Oh that's true! (interjection of sudden realization)
Did you hear the sound?
What else is there to hear but your voice?
Don't argue. - A bomb!
Climb down. Cover your ears.
Why did I cover my ears and still hear the answer?
It's my family heirloom
You're obviously trying to piss me off, aren't you?
You don't have to mess with the fire. It's big enough already.
If you're not happy to come back, don't come back. No one's asking you to
come back.
You told me it was your birthday, so I came back.
Do you think I like coming back?
Where are you going?
Eat Wonton Noodles
Answer me. To go or not to go?
not go
It's so annoying. Just call again and we'll go.
Let's go.
tomboy
What are you ashamed of? The rice is already cooked. Come out and make
coffee.
I got it. The second girl.
It's a ballet.
Tonight at the Event Center
The show is over. We're leaving for Japan first thing in the morning.
Then we're gonna do it tonight.
When I was there.
It must be my call, huh?
Let's do it tonight.
You two get your stuff over there.
What are you two doing here?
We are
It's a fan. I know.
The backstage is important. No one is allowed in.
It's almost your turn. Don't get ready to go. Come on.
Why is there a baby swan?
She's a back-up swan.
Back up. I know. It's backstage preparation.
I don't need you to explain. Go on, go on.
Who told you to wear those clothes?
It's you guys.
Come on, let's go get them.
Go, go, go! Get him!
What the hell? I've been hit.
There it is. I don't see it.
That way.
It's our turn. Come on.
Director, you won the Golden Horse.
You can't spice it up anytime either
What spice? They're here to make a mess.
Don't you run.
Get him to the backstage! Get him to the backstage!
What? Put me down! Put me down!
That's the one. Put me down. Do you hear me?
Watch out, I'm coming.
accomplish
Oh, my God.
Not that one. Put it down.
I'm sorry.
It's this one.
Is that her, Dad?
How could this happen? I can't even look at it.
Great! Great!
I see the audience likes this kind of stuff. I'm breaking through again.
Let's go. We're getting off the stage.
That's great. That's great. Get out there and keep dancing.
You dance.
Go? Go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
NANCY, NANCY, come back, NANCY!
That way down.
Go to the curtain. Go to the curtain.
The curtain falls. The curtain falls.
Good, good, good.
The lights are falling.
Come on, get back up. I'm sorry.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
What are you doing?
Just change your clothes quickly. Don't get in the way.
That way.
What are you looking at?
Cheers
According to my computer's analysis.
The clue left by Mouthwater's death was two hearts.
If you erase these two hearts, you're left with a bunch of words.
Mizukuisen always likes to do things horizontally.
Then let's look at it sideways.
The first line is MAP
It's a map.
Smart
Wasn't Kusuiquan always emphasizing Kowloon before he died?
So let's take a look at the map of Kowloon
The second line is P6
P6
It's the sea.
Not bad.
So what's the final clue, B3?
What?
Then I don't know.
B3 is this buoy.
Not bad.
Your partner is really something.
Just like you.
That's right. The diamond must be under the buoy.
Must be.
Oh, no. I can't swim.
Neither will I.
I'll get you down first.
That's how it works.
You fucking bald guy.
Found it.
Don't you run. I'll catch up.
Don't chase him. That bag is a fake. It's really here.
You're still good.
Dead bald guy.
You're just in time.
You can have the diamond back. I'm not guilty, am I?
It's done.
What are you doing here again?
I'll bring the car to you.
You should go back. The white glove smells like a police officer.
It wouldn't have happened.
If you need anything, just call me. I've brought a thousand men to help
you.
Come on, let's go.
Go back and put water in my bath.
Got it!
ALBERT, PUT YOUR CLOTHES ON, YOU'LL GET COLD.
Fake kindness, afraid I'd smuggle it in, staring at me with a radio.
See how you stare.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hurry up.
It's not fast.
I thought you said you'd laid a net.
You can't reveal the truth. It's either you or him this time.
And you?
I'm just waiting to see how you two die.
The White Glove's coming after us. Come on.
I think it's his death, not yours.
That's not right. The two of us bullying him.
Give you a chance to show off.
And you?
I'm saving it for the big show.
That's a big scene, isn't it? Your turn.
That's great... we'll get rid of all the horses.
What army?
Calling a man-child with a radio?
I threw away the radio.
What?
What? You said you had a net set up.
I don't have a net here.
Oh, no, you're useless. Let me do it. Let me do it.
Don't move. Let me do it.
Be careful. Be careful.
Let me do it.
Don't move. Go.
Stop the car. Stop the car. Stop the car.
Get back! Get back!
Surrender! He surrendered! He surrendered!
You're useless. You're just like a car. You're a good-looking, useless
thing.
Stop it. Ask them to eat the pineapple.
Underneath
Good idea.
You're doing good, little man.
I see so many stars.
Are you okay?
Not at the moment.
Get over there. Come on.
What's up?
dig a hole in the ground
Digging a hole in the ground
What is it?
It's a net!
Ha! That was fun.
careful
Let me have a good time.
Get out of the way.
I want to escape.
I'll come.
Don't move.
Yeah, you're good at it.
That's not a cover.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I have something.
You don't mind, do you?
Help. I can't swim.
What are you doing? Nothing to see. Go away.
What are you doing? Get out of the way. Get out of the way.
How's he doing now?
There's nothing to see. Go away.
Come down. Come down.
Let him go.
Dr. Lam, he's coming up too.
Let him go. One's a freak, one's a psycho.
It's a perfect match. Drive.
Thank you.
You're a man, crying like a woman. I'm laughing.
lit. hairy spleen
If there's a conflict, you and I can do it.
Put aside your fears and sit down to talk
You need help, I'll help.
It doesn't matter how hard it is.
You're by my side, and I'm no longer on the sidelines.
Both of them are brave.
I'm all set.
You won't panic.
Best Partner
If there's a conflict, you and I can do it.
Put aside your fears and sit down to talk
You need help, I'll help.
It doesn't matter how hard it is.
You're by my side, and I'm no longer on the sidelines.
Both of them are brave.
I'm all set.
You can rest in peace
Best Partner
I'm the best partner.
Always the best partner