Thanks a lot.
Wow, Maki-chan! Vu low
The old trustees ﹥ the son and
Yes, no. LIFT is bad.
SORRY, BYE.
Mee-woo!
Drink! Hustle, hustle, hustle! Unh!
Do you have a good understanding of the world?
I'll give you a head start.
I don't want the whole thing.
And you've got a great ride. - Oh, forced laughter.
It's hot with Indian curry.
I'm sorry, you bastard. Old Dou told me to do as you say.
I'll cover you up. You're in the salt water.
I know, I'm wrong.
The next step is to choke on your own.
Airplane
Same as
Yacht
B
Choke on it, don't worry, put the paper down.
Don't go now, yo!
Yes, paper pigeons, paper songs
Come on!
Bye. - Bye.
Hello, Roberto.
Hello, good to see you.
Are you having a good time in Hong Kong?
I'm sorry.
Godfather, don't pretend.
I'm all right.
He waits for you and sees that you have good luck.
HUMAN
roast antonio
Go ahead, Aimee.
Bake António, right?
Do you have a U?
What's wrong with you?
roast antonio
You give me a hard time every time you have something to do.
I know which side is sighing.
White Hand Daisy
What about him?
Venice
I believe you.
I won't do it, Godfather.
You go to Hong Kong and help me with the diamond stall?
What do you mean, pick me?
Do as I say, or you'll die.
You can use our suo Hong Kong brown relationship
I could do without the diamonds.
But do not let the Italians lose face!
I'm British!
Loggerheads
Don't you know that Britain and Italy are cousins?
I've never heard of it.
Put down the diamond, or you'll die.
According to the survey ...
You and Kikiya must not talk about Saisoi
You can say anything.
Wah, you talk.
Recent relationships
Tsim Sha Tsui Centre
A serious incident of wiring robbery occurred
A group of diamond salaries worth a fortune were looted.
No one has reported the case.
We have obtained the following information
This is a member of the local Mumbai triad.
He is called Szeto Buren and he steals rats.
This is a newcomer to the international smuggling syndicate
He is an Italian called Montezzuto.
In the case of the single robbery.
There is no sigh of loss in the case of Szeto.
And this Italian, he didn't even report the case.
What about the low line?
It's just a white hand sock.
As for the sale of further information, there is a void.
The above information is from our source
From our land.
As he shouted about his special status
That's why we can't make your name public.
The whistle, the snake, Ming's?
Noisy, don't break the century atmosphere
This is the world's most famous thief.
He is called "White Hand Socks" and specializes in robbing diamonds and gold
He has seven passports, eight names, nine identities
Two sexes are buried together
It's not a case in Hong Kong.
You can talk to Hong Kong people about brownies.
It can also be said that Hong Kong people are unhappy
Therefore, we must have specific rules.
Put her on the market.
Dead right?
Yes, he has two rivals.
The first one is the Pink Panther Red Petershaker.
It is a pity that he has been called by the Lord
The second one is that he is ...
Don't stop Chiu!
Drinking in the United States
For fucks sake, white socks.
He changed from a flower to a wordless flower
From Chai Tau to Bald Head
At the same time he ordered him, by a mark on his face, to do so within three months.
If you can't catch a white sock
We need to make an early contribution to the pension scheme and wash the dumplings
Therefore, we decided to invite the lamb-headed grandfather to visit Hong Kong.
Because he is the most enthusiastic about catching white socks and shouting at people
As for the most outstanding young female Superintendent of Police in Jiaochuan this year
What about the poem of Ho Tung?
A man's wife!
We'll send him.
The Office of the Inspector General of the Kwong Tau Estate
What a choke! What a choke!
Hustle Keti, is there a fire?
Silence, little sister! Yes!
I've got fire all around me.
But it's a good one, yo.
Secret Nun Fake Authentic Brown Hustle
I want to see the relationship.
Oh, it's a mess!
Good blink!
Brown, fire, fire, fire, fire, fire.
My gun goes off all the time, Joe Koo.
It's all her fault. It's none of my business, Ada.
I don't dare to go down there.
Go away, you're the best of the day!
I am?
I pay you to die.
Is a vegetable stalk a vegetable bush?
Let's go.
Have you seen a woman with a big spleen in the village?
Oh, I have a gun bag for you in the morning.
What about the police superintendent, who is in charge of the light-headed detectors?
I'll have to take it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
So many people, how can you do it?
You'll agree with me if I make a big bel belch.
She's ready to go now
People on the Edge!
Well, well, well!
Mimi, go!
Don't move your lips!
You, Chung, go!
Shut up! Shut up!
No one is here. Oh, my God!
I'll cover up my identity with you. What? Do you have any information?
There are three singles, two are firm, and one is a stream of shouting
Then speak two languages and be quiet.
That's the American bald guy.
The boss sent you to help him with his investigation.
You know all the information about my place.
Don't do that.
What is it?
Yes, that's right.
Some people in Kowloon City are trying to rob Chow Tai Fook Gold Company on Sunday.
Do you know that today is the day?
I'm with him.
Is it a good day?
But it's not a good day.
Noisy, is there a single whisper?
What's that?
It's just that the boss said you wouldn't pick up the plane at the airport today.
Just send me around the living ancient
But, I'm sorry, I've knocked you down.
It's really darker than ink beans
Oh, yeah?
Howl!
I'm going to investigate the case.
Check the choking case.
It's none of your business. It's all about Jacky Chan.
Clouds vs. Water, Thunder vs. Wind
White fruit vs.
The Great Four Joys
small phase
It's not addictive.
My name is Chan Pak Keung.
My name is Au Sui Keung.
My name is a shame.
I'm all right.
Hello, old man.
For a while, someone was choking on your salary.
Hey, don't be proud of me, suona.
Mee-woo, robbing Ham, driving.
Mee-woo, do it already!
All buried in the corner, yo!
The cry is full of it, yo!
Look at the "What?
Note to all units
Kowloon City Chow Tai Fook Gold Company Kiss Alert
Let's go and see what happened to Koo Fat Sang.
Zhou Da Zhan Jin Shop suona Ding?
And that's a kiss.
Go, go, go.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Okay, go get a car. Okay, Mimi.
I'm so stingy, I'll blow your head off if you go back in.
Mickey!
Big Brother, get rid of the forced laughter.
You're chasing me!
Drive
Get out of the car, the police will use you to set up the car.
What about the saw keys?
Gimmicky Un... ha! Ha! Ha]
Hurry up, Debbie. Hurry up, Un, baldy.
If you want to feel ashamed of leaving, it's easy to do it quickly.
Make it sweet. I want to die.
Do you want to send us to an ambulance?
I'll kill you with one shot. Be careful.
Drive in anger
You bald-headed Un, you're a car. Oh, you want to die?
- No, it's not.
z VIII z VIII
Go, go, go...
Damn, you order a Jet Car, Joe.
Sao Sao Play ether.
I'm a policeman in America.
You're a policeman. You haven't even gotten rid of your country voice.
Have you just been smuggled in?
No, it's not.
You can buy all these things everywhere.
Selling three cones in Temple Street.
I caught a bribe for you. Take a look.
It's in!
Let's hear it.
The four edges of your earth are the big one.
godfather
The same as the case on the ground.
Bearded man, you're with me.
Go. - Go.
Sit.
Well... Related.
Drink, Pei.
Okay, okay, okay.
good
You're not to blame for walking.
Are you familiar with the laws of Hong Kong, country bumpkin?
Hong Kong legislation is not familiar
American law is familiar to you.
The landlord, Quaran, learns to rob
The time has fallen.
Don't like it.
Swim in the water.
I'm leaving the plane for Joe.
Do you have any friends in Hong Kong?
Not for my relatives, not for my friends.
He knows that if I shout, there is one
It's the edge.
Hong Kong
He called me and asked me to come, Joe.
Ding, ding, ding, ding!
Countryman, I'll sing you a song.
You may not do it, if you want to scare me.
It can be used as a showcase in the future.
What is the name of the choke?
ALBERR Qiao A Shi, Ou Shuiqiang
Hey, the whole continent is crying out with the English language.
How can you be so powerful in the countryside?
Taishan
The marriage has not yet been consummated.
What about you?
What's the matter with you, sex?
Ahjumma, I have a whisker.
Then what is it again?
A man is a man if he's got beard brown, just like you.
The head is not like a man, and the body is not like a woman
And now they are neither male nor female
You're begging and choking. - Don't shush.
Are you kidding?
I won't hit you, you hit me!
Ha, what a choke, what a choke, what a choke!
But the name is true.
I don't think so. Auntie, you're choking.
Superintendent He's choking.
It's working fast, but it's slow to take the gun.
I'm the Commissioner of Police.
Help you with this case, Joe.
He's so worried.
To protect your brown identity from the noise.
I've arranged for you to be married as husband and wife.
What are you talking about? He's playing my husband.
He's a loser. He's not worthy of being my husband.
She's a deadbeat.
含 ， 吨 吨 吨 ， 元 女 包 ， 我 殷 你
Fatty, let's go to the hotel together.
Put it down. - Yuck.
I'm singing, I'm leaving the room.
I'm going to be her husband.
You! Think!
Huh? A-x... -jˊl...
I'm going to do it.
I'm not used to staying in hotels, so I dare to stay in my house
You House Enterprise?
You're a beauty!
You're taking over her house and there's a ghost in it.
Noisy, bald guy, you don't want to be with my girl
All the police stations are clear. I'm a man, Joe.
Remember...
We're a couple. You're so cute.
I'm sorry, I've never seen it before.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
According to the information provided by the Border Control Unit
Drinking diamonds is what this pretty boy does.
His name is King Kong and he is known as the Flying Toad
She has a partner called "The Eye".
She is called Sze Shui Chuen, known as the Lady's Pool.
You're looking at her. She's a woman's phone.
She never showed up after her two kissing sessions.
Kim just lived on the fifth floor of this building.
Item 1 King
Hey, Kim Lee, it's Soo Sang.
And I was called by a different name...
Red Cat CALL Black Cat OVER
The black cat hears the panting and speaks smack
Report to Black Cat. I'm going to bury the diamond.
You're talking about diamond peanuts again
I'll take the bawl, and I'll talk to you.
If you don't talk better than I do, I'll start [Diao Meng Noise
I know, but you know.
If I don't talk more than you, I can't do it
What do you mean?
Because I'm a barking maniac!
Unh! You're so bilious!
Fuyan, you're dead!
Why don't you go out and get a restaurant?
Good Un, Bian Qun Un?
I'm not as good as you.
You don't know what I'm singing.
I'm quieter than you are, and you listen to the dusty black cat.
Relationship Seventh Heaven Restaurant
I can't hear you. Speak up!
It's so stupid.
A sick cat in a seventh heaven restaurant
Come on, D, go to Seventh Heaven Restaurant for coffee. Black Cat is waiting for you.
You're so noisy.
Diamond Pack, Dbitu Black Cat!
It's not diamonds, it's peanuts.
It's him.
Oh! White hand socks! It's him! Return it
King Kong!
Oh, my God!
Let's go, Kim!
No, Jo, it's not him, it's another Un!
Wow, what a show of life!
According to the old car first
Dead man's bag!
Bye, baldy.
I'll get you, I'll get you, I'll get you.
Flying Toad, go away!
Stop the car. I'm a cop.
Granny, bye, bye.
Stop the car!
More than a dozen of them.
What's going on?
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
No, no, peanuts!
Drink peanuts, I'll be safe.
I will keep this a secret.
Why are the two women different?
Saying brown makes you so nervous
If you don't get nervous, you'll fake gasping.
Tell the secret than listen to a bawl
It's more noisy than a man's melon before he's halfway through.
Don't be afraid, don't listen to the bawling
Say it!
Bawling, drilling, stone... yo.
Do it already.
I've been shot, can't you see?
Open a bottle of champagne on the ground. What? Say something.
Hey, it's not safe here. Go to the toilet.
Get the brown, get the blame.
Come on, yo. Say it, smack.
I will wrap the diamond ... I will wrap the peanut to disturb suo jiulong ...
Hey, don't say that.
What do you mean?
Don't be afraid, even if you talk.
Oh, I can't hear you anymore.
Hey, he's mute. He didn't even talk about begging. Let's go.
What are you doing?
Maniac!
Unh, unh, unh, unh!
Hey, go through the back door.
It's in!
Hey, there's no one there. Say something.
Bawl, peanut spread...
Noisy, do you find this LIFTT good?
Morning. Right side.
Morning. Left side.
Take care of the back.
Unh-unh, don't be proud, it's a ghost.
You're a ghost!
We are talking about the restoration of the Qing Dynasty.
Shaolin and Saki ask for honesty
The Remains of the Burning of the Red Lotus Monastery, not to be smacked
What? Choke? Well, oh?
That means repeating every word for one more disaster.
You're almost there.
Bawl, bawl, bawl, bawl, bawl, bawl.
Stalls, wiring, nine, nine, nine, nine
You're talking about choking.
Have some peanut butter.
"Well, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Even a little girl knows how to speak brown, how many silkworms do you have?
Well, there's no one at LIEFT
wait for
Drink, Pei.
Black cat, what am I doing?
You have to remember the Un, Mae Sum Phen.
Baa! Mae Wan!
Red Cat, what about you?
I'm not. You saw it all.
I'll sing, and I'll be home for half a day.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, but I don't care about you.
You can't have peanuts.
Don't worry about the red cat, remember
No matter what, Wing Sum is the best photographer in Hong Kong.
Red Cat is stingy ...
I've got the white sock.
No, they are not white socks
White hands and socks, red beard and eyes, ahjumma
I guarantee he's robbing diamonds...
BERT
She doesn't look like a thief
Well, it seems.
There is a way. You can try it than me and you'll see.
Lai Lai?
I'm a student in Scotland...
The tweezers have to be used.
But you're gonna work with me, Joe.
I‥I
Sir, please sit down
Don't do it. Sit down. Sit down.
Before my law is consumed
I won't answer any questions.
We're playing an IQ game.
We're waiting for my lawyer to be silenced.
Do you know that I am already in water?
Not allergic to howling
I was studying in America at Scotland Yard.
NO.1 Chinese Bald Detective
You're afraid you've heard my name.
Oh, I've heard the sound.
Our cooperation with forced laughter
But wait for me to speak first.
Dead Man's Bag
Carry a hand and devour it!
I don't want to be stingy with you, you know...
Unh-unh-unh! I have not let go.
Hey, hey, you're so messy!
Silence. - Yeah.
Sir, we are playing games.
Yes!
Let's play a game of reactions.
You carry a hand out and a man pounces on it.
If the opponent wins, he wins on the other side.
Then who is going to do it first?
I'll take your hand.
Oh, you look at me like that.
It's my turn to scream.
Don't play.
Carry a hand out and devour
The side is stingy, it's a sure thing.
Wailing
Is it this one?
Drink.
Oh, my God!
Hustle. My turn to howl.
Where's my gun, you son of a bitch?
What about the degree?
Drink, don't make me noisy.
What are you doing?
Hey, are you playing?
There is one
I've been playing with it since I was a kid, and I won it.
What's the point?
Let you go.
Come on, forced laughter.
It's so simple. The right hand is holding the ear.
Hold a floor with your left hand, turn, turn, turn five times
Then, they went to the stall to bawl a beer.
If you get it, you win.
I don't think you want to work with me.
No, you show me how to do it. I'll do it first.
It's so easy to be a good boy, just like the song "The Little Brother".
Adopt an ear to live under the ground
Head DUP DUP, tail Eeyi Eeyi
First turn, Chrysanthemum Garden; second turn, Blind Dragon Boat
In the third turn, the back is sore. In the fourth turn, the breath is dull.
Fifth turn, soft feet
Ming?
Ming-Ya, silence!
Hey, turn to the edge first.
Choke, are you really waxing?
Stay with me. - Oh, my God.
Slowly.
I can use the fastener. I'll live with you. What?
Wow, it's so restless, it's on the verge of five circles.
You got it. You got it. I'm on my third one.
The fourth brown, the exorcism, the fifth la?
I'll take a bite. I'll take a bite. I'll take a bite.
Come on.
First turn, Chrysanthemum Garden; second turn, Blind Dragon Boat
In the third turn, the back is sore. In the fourth turn, the breath is dull.
The fifth turn, the feet are soft, the sixth turn ....
To Bitterness
Bye. - Bye.
It's really a loss of water.
I've made five turns before.
He has already made a lot of noise and choked.
Take a break.
Item 1 King
I'm a white sock. I want to be with you.
You'll have to wait a while to kill me
What do you mean?
It is because some people are fighting against the clock.
Un, big brother, stop! Stop!
Damn pretty boy, you'd better go, I'll go home to work
Class Ma?
It's her coffee, mention her
Un call the superintendent, he's holding the door open and howling.
Okay, step two.
know
Someone has hit me.
You're wrong, you're wrong. I'm a white knight.
I have a gift for you. Go to the door.
What? Choke on it?
Wings, what are the means?
The same bawling method of selling diamonds is exactly the same as the noise
Chan Pak Cheung, it's your turn for forced laughter
No, I'll do it.
You can't get out.
Go straight out!
Look behind you.
If you're not with me, you're dead today.
Thank you for saving my life.
You are reporting to me?
And when I, the lawyer, have been devoured, I shall speak of the blame.
Hey, hey, hey... you save me from the silence.
I've been looking into the diamond bawling case lately.
It's not me.
Then I'm looking for the wrong person.
Un, 吽, 係吝, 係吝, 我謳啡, 我謳咎
It's me doing the noise, it's me doing the sh...
What about the diamonds?
I don't know.
You don't want to click me, my hands are soft
Noisy, don't be so soft, I'll at most talk about devouring
So, what's the edge of the diamond?
Red Cat, collect the ball!
Where are the red cats?
She is so noisy
You've been chasing me again.
Hey, Lah, come on.
At most, I'll let you get a bag of diamonds.
Yes, after the bunting of the diamonds
I want you to help me with the white socks, Joe.
Okay, no. You have to promise me one thing.
What is it?
Afterwards, don't tell me the noise.
I'll make sure you're okay.
How can you guarantee that?
I swear.
Bomb ready?
Net ready.
Take it up.
What are you listening to?
Oh, it's so tight in the morning.
You send a side up there?
carnation
It is noisy!
Oh, you relax. It's hot, it's not loud.
What is the place?
I can't stay for one more minute to sneeze.
What are you talking about?
It's a big deal!
Eat! You've got it, carbonic acid.
The lack of color, aroma and flavor is really disgusting.
You son of a bitch!
Look at this lamb-head, he lacks upbringing
It is disgusting to ask me to live in the same room with them.
Yes, the air is dirty.
The lack of air is simply a source of indifference.
Noisy, you can't make a sound even if she dies
The bomb site?
Go on, yawn. Go make noise.
Even the sound of the doorbell is too loud.
Do it already.
I'm sending shoes, Joe.
It's my sister.
Put it down!
[Jus
I can't be coy about this.
And you two are working together.
Gimmick my house.
You. Okay.
What about me?
I'm all right.
Sister, what are you doing? Don't insult her!
She has red eyes.
Sister, which one of these two is silent?
Well, wait for me.
This one, you don't know anything about it
This one, there's no need to use the coffee.
Sit.
Hey! Hey, do you want to have a brownie?
Unh! Let's go! Let's go!
Don't breathe, sit down for a while and go first
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're going to Japan?
evade
Do business.
No, it's the world.
Hey!
You don't see it, do you?
It's like a pretty boy has been hit by a head drop when he sees your girl
Now she doesn't even know that you're begging for old beans
Well, you old bean, what are you doing?
I don't even know.
Did you steal the diamond?
It's me. Steal it, Joe.
Collect the burying and swallowing edge.
Red Cat Buried
Mr. Kwong, do you know what you are looking for?
She wrote the secret on these two women.
The two girls are so dark that they can't be seen.
There... you.
I have found two daughters in my previous life.
Hey, bald guy, you heard me.
I've said that the only thing I've done is to steal coffee from this pretty boy.
Do you have me?
What about you?
I'm just a skinhead. I'm the same.
Not even you.
Noisy, you have caught my hand.
What are you doing, men?
You hear that smack?
Only this pretty boy knows that diamonds are sold.
I, for my part, give the order.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to get a diamond before I get a diamond.
Keep her safe and sound.
Shit, Achanla's feet of bombs went up and howled.
What are you talking about?
Well!
Achang, go up to the stall and drop a bomb.
Don't have enough time to howl
Point.
There is enough time to get on, not enough time to get off.
I don't care. In any case, I don't want to pay you to blow him up.
Noisy, are you still here?
I'll go, you see!
It's airy and refreshing, and your head is bare.
Oh, yo, the steak's pretty again, but your sister's a bitch.
What are you choking on?
Goo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Even the doorbell sounds good.
I can open the door with a bang.
Wrong delivery!
Wrong delivery, you're a worm.
A shoebox is heavy, don't worry about it.
You, big guy, Joe.
What is the name and phone number of the woman who watched the incident?
This is the work of a specialist in the field. I hope he will remember it.
Hey, Sok-an To, shoot the hard file and then help me with the earnest.
Recently, Hao Suo has been making a lot of noise.
I'm crying. It's not a girl's name, it's a phone forced laughter.
She's all over the place. I don't remember that much.
Has she encountered any girls recently?
Yes, two Tims
But it's so outrageous that I have to pick them.
What kind of mouth do you like to kiss? You should remember that.
If everyone can remember
Then I don't need a computer.
No! And the family is happy to have a cup and less noise
The diamond shouting opportunity is not so good again.
You're going to be in the brownies again, yo.
You and me, yo.
If you shrink, you'll be happy, but it's hard to snap.
Relationship
What about when Shi Shui-sheung was about to die?
A big belch.
I suspect he may have a girl friend.
It's called "Rose".
Precedent
What's the matter with you?
Relationship.
Then, you must help me to take a picture.
Point.
It is because where a person has been introduced and shouted at
I've been asked to shadow shop
Photo Gallery Remembrance Noise
Well, the oral water....
Don't use it, don't use it, don't use it.
It's all right.
Rose Sam?
Madam, we don't have a relationship with each other.
Beer, not a shadow.
I'm so sorry.
I'd like to share a date with a friend.
The edge.
Has anyone had a nude photo shoot lately?
Rowan?
So you're a friend of Rowan Brown?
No, I'm a friend of the Fountain of Lips.
Don't you know you're a beggar, country bumpkin?
This is the phone number of a girl who has a full body.
I don't know what she's whining about all day.
Take a sip of water.
Oh, I know. A red cat?
That's right.
Drink up, you poor bastard! I'm sorry, but I've never seen anything.
Drink, yo. It's good for me.
No, I don't even know where the spasticity is
I don't want to make any noise.
I recommend you to help me...
Well, when I'm quiet, you go keep the door open.
If there's a gag, it's a gag.
You're dead, smack.
Hey, what are you doing?
Tablet 0
I've got a husband yelling.
Nothing
I'm so old. Shh. Brown.
Mmm, high. Okay.
I'm not pretty again
Yes.
What is it?
She doesn't recognize my style of forced laughter.
You're wearing one, don't you think she looks like you?
Don't do it.
I'll give you a chance to have a relationship with me at most.
Enough.
But Ding! Both of them.
I've got the blame.
The first girl asked suo to do this.
For a while, I'll be the one to talk about Jin.
What do you mean?
First of all, Grandpa, you take care of me.
Is this a girl from a later age? Is she looking at me?
That's not necessary.
I've been in Chinatown before.
The most glamorous brown men's election howl
Result
I have to.
How many people have participated in the event?
Well, I'll take one.
For a while, I talked about the blame.
I'm not a lawyer, I'm a lawyer.
I'm the one who's going to tell the story.
Heh !
Whoo !
What have you done?
Oh, okay, time for coffee.
What are you doing first?
He hit me on the waist and hit me on the head.
I've been talking about Jin for a while, don't make a sound
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait for me to tell the story.
I want to talk.
Long Village
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Traffic vehicle hitting traffic light at entrance of the Kowloon Motorway
The traffic is really bad.
Hey, taxi service station, you know?
93, the old lady asked you if you were going to eat at the house.
If you know my wife, I won't be able to get to her at any time.
Mary, I'm asking you to have dinner.
Good, but don't be idle this morning
A MARY, Sister Un, EI
Who are you?
I'm a barrister.
This is him, Uncle Yuen Wong.
A woman
The water phase is so full of claws
I don't know where she died.
You've killed him!
She's really dead!
But go to hell. Go to the side. We don't know.
What a sigh!
Unh! He died a horrible death!
When he was dying of brown
Mr. Go, tell him your name.
She called me by my name even before she died.
H 炎 ‧ IE
There is a man who doesn't want to see Nezha.
Please inform the taxi service counter at the side.
Mr CHAN, this girl really has [sympathy].
Blessed be God... bawling a northern dog
He has an inheritance.
How many of them are left behind?
Into 500,000 Joe
Howl for money!
Wow, hello. Oh, what a surprise.
A dog from the north is making money
Thank you, God. Thank you. [Diao Shuihao
The grandfather is stingy, and the God of Heaven has choked and devoured him.
You've got no place to go, Petain.
Oh, thank you.
However, it is not yet processed in Hong Kong.
We must first prove your identity.
Oh, come on, I have an identity card. Listen.
Oh, no! I would like to share with you, please...
The body is so special.
You're a bastard, and you're even talking about it.
I'm bawling. I'm drunk. What?
Oh, beg you to drink.
"Noisy, know how to eat, chirp, and relationship.
A fire truck is available at the Dry Point Fire Station.
Chung Yes
Hong Kong colonies have been drinking from coffin trolleys and carts of dead people.
It's so annoying.
Your land is ridiculous.
Parrot wants to see my sister's ass!
Wow, look at the 500 000 howls!
I can't even see 500,000 if I look at it
You've made it!
If you don't pay your salary, your eyes will be in the right place.
Oh, so the estate is automatically transferred to pay him.
Ah Wong Tenant Throat Hustle
Un, then you have begged and choked to prove that he is his core?
I love Fortuna
Where do we go?
The Government should drink at this level, so that it can show its own face to itself.
Then, don't be afraid to say "yes" for the sake of love.
Unh-unh... good meat and sour shout.
Half a million questions...
I don't have any silver.
I've got it, girl.
Hey, don't allow me to repeat it
Remember...
It's not a face, it's a memo
Hey, she's with a female film student
Go and visit a Hong Kong girl.
Brother
Mr. Hustle is happy to see you.
That's right. Bye.
Hey, Mickey, live.
Two of them.
Wow, Brother Sing, Puru.
Is it your own water?
He's just a maniac.
I don't even want to see her sigh.
The two dwellings are in their own water.
It's an accident.
I'm not even prepared!
Noisy, bad environment, howling
Don't worry, we have two brothers in the world.
You're not as loud as I am, are you?
Hey, I don't know who's in this place, but I'm a madman.
You're bold enough to be on the edge, but I'm a nude girl.
What is the edge of the sale offer?
Hey, one person is dead.
Two of them can fight for serious injuries.
Shoot the hard file and spit it out!
Oh, nothing.
Tell me, which one is the vendor?
Two persons
The bridge is on the other side.
Come on out, lace!
Which one is it? Ask my sister to take a picture first.
齊 齊 開 [ 刁
Yes.
Both of them.
What a choke!
What is the noise, and what is the home?
Don't be proud of it.
Which one is it?
Un, it's me for a while.
What a pain in the ass!
Do you have a copy?
Proverbially, yo, live and let live.
He lied and howled first
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Don't be afraid of the noise.
I'm going to let you go if I can.
Hey, yo, it's my turn to scream.
My nose is not big enough for you.
I have to shake a lot.
Jo, yo, yo, yo.
Oh, I'm on it.
I really don't want to go up there again.
Noisy, it's my turn to be brown, I'm so sheepish.
You call me Chee.
Chee.
Un, Yegor devour!
"I'm going to get a new one," he said.
Imitation of the Seventh Day of the Year (Quat 7)
How much more do you have to shake, apparently?
You son of a bitch!
Let me fall, you want to kill me?
Un, don't let me go. I'm dead. I'm dead.
But you didn't die until the noise.
You're dead. I'm not dead.
If I don't talk like that, why would you let me go?
All right, drink up. My turn, yo.
I'm going to shake it, Ben.
You are not angry!
You're all crazy, and you talk about righteousness and shivering!
You bald-headed bastard, you told me to move first.
In fact, it's all your fault.
So you sigh.
No bites, no brownies, including a few more knives.
You're a deadbeat. You want to lend me a knife.
Fat nephew, you actually want your sister to take a picture of her.
Oh, my God, Sing is not even calling.
Call Fatty, Brother Sing.
I'll call him Fatty
It's better than calling him a tortoise star behind your back.
What are you choking on?
You bastard, if you want to shake, you can do it.
♪ Choke, you and I will smack ♪
I am most familiar with this place, no trains.
No trains.
Ah! No fire engine!
"You'll have to be like this on all sides of the earth.
It's so trivial to ask for hospitalization.
We have to designate the same layer.
I've been so stingy, I've blocked a ball from turning.
If you're choking on something, just keep calling me.
All right.
Rising Sun I
You need to assume that I am not there.
I'm going out for a choke.
Ha ha!
I have a chance with Doraemon.
You're not in good hands with the poor lady.
I don't think so. I don't want to yell at her.
It's no use yelling at him. He's so pathetic.
What about the two dead guys?
Choke, grieve 3
"The wicked, the silent, the smack.
Don't go, I want you to help me.
You need a dead man!
I can't believe they dumped me and went to check on Hsuan.
I'm going to make a mess of it.
Koo, begging, you can't say that Ho Tung-sze is a wicked woman.
He's my dream lover. He's evil, of course.
But it's all about women's coffee.
Why can't you see her gentle and whispery side?
I am not sure if you know, but I am following him.
She's a grandma who sneezes.
You see brown, when did I cross my waist on the ground?
She didn't bother me half a word.
What's the point of being a steel charity show?
She sits low, just like a little girl howling
Never bridge a leg, Joe.
She's good.
Don't you believe it? Wait for it to go silent. You sing it.
B Working day
When did you get into the noise and devour Joe?
Oh, don't you want to parry? I want to tell you...
Say it.
Listen to my birthday.
Ha, ha, ha, you lose me.
You're in it again.
Do I have a shirt?
What? Choke on it?
I, Auntie
Bite, my sister has done it.
I've never seen her like this before.
She's not bothered
You'd better book a bed with him at the nunnery.
Hello, ma'am.
Your sister is on the phone.
A ton, but dang.
Well, I'm on the phone outside.
Item 1 King
Grandma, I am Snake Ming
Damn you, you snake!
I told you to check the maniacs.
You and your family have to call me first.
He's still a hard man.
You'll have to give her a break.
What?
He wants to be a bald man, you can talk to me and pay him
If he is not a nephew, I will be his nephew
Yes, if I knew you were interested in me
I'll hit you!
I'm going to make a melon.
I know. You go out and smack it.
The whole temple
clinch
Again? - Yeah.
Fine, get it done.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Bye, you.
God bless you!
You want to fight, pretty boy?
You're fighting me again?
Noisy, it's my wife's birthday today
Okay, go keep her company.
you
Oh, my God!
I'd like to make a light bulb
Tell the truth
I'm going out, but Doraemon.
Un, do what?
The black centipede is a noisy watch for people to cut.
Alberg, do you see me begging for the same boo tonight?
This is a good idea.
The boss sent you to Temple Street to be a crouch
The whole thing is dirty.
Listen to me on my birthday.
Then what is it again?
Open feet and financial services
The steak is already full of water and noise.
I'll do it myself.
You're the first one to make a whole lot of noise.
Drought III
It's delicious!
The day of your birth.
Relationship.
How old are you?
Thirty years old
Congratulations to you.
Gong, you howl!
"Containing, not a man, thirty-one flowers.
A woman who is 30 years old is a tea scum.
It is not even 30 years old.
No one is yelling?
So what?
Did you hear that?
Apart from your voice, what kind of voice do you have?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Lower your ears.
The talk I heard, the talk I heard.
Where is the voice?
Un, I'm not ready.
Hey, you're obviously compelling me to stir up the fire.
You've got the fire up and out.
If you don't want to gag, you don't want to gag.
No one told you to go back to silence, Joe.
And today is your birthday. I'm on my way.
You're making me want to giggle.
You go to the border.
Eat Wun Tun
Answer me. - I'll go.
Well, go.
You're so frightened, you can't say it again.
Go.
"Your name is Theo Khoi, and you look like Sugar".
" The Fresh & Fresh Look
" My name is KING RKONG
" Item looks like JAMES BOND
" Best File ヘルメンズ
"You decide on water, I add milk and sugar.
"You wash the table and I'll wash the table!
"I'll help you get rid of your money, you help me clear my position
" Best File ヘルメンズ
"There's begging and choking. You and I are not demons.
"Wipe off the blame and sit down and talk"
"You need a hand, I'll give a hand.
"All the hardships are not worthwhile.
"You are at my side, I am no longer at a loss"
"A pair of rickets are strong.
"I am all for sale"
"You won't be surprised.
" Best File ヘルメンズ
Shit! Shit!
"There's begging and choking. You and I are not demons.
"Wipe off the blame and sit down and talk"
"You need a hand, I'll give a hand.
"All the hardships are not worthwhile.
"You are at my side, I am no longer at a loss"
"A pair of rickets are strong.
"I am all for sale"
" You can have a safe trip
" Best File ヘルメンズ
"The Best of Our Land"
"Always the Best Shot"
Complaining, begging, choking, ugly, no.
The rice is already cooked, and two cups of coffee are served.
Hey, I got it.
The second girl, who used to dance the Pyrenees
We'll do the last SHOW at the Grand Ballroom tonight.
I'll go to Japan early in the morning.
That's why we're so depressed tonight.
When I was there, it was all about me.
friends
My hands are full tonight.
Item 1 King
Do you need a shush to move the yo-yo to the boo-boo?
Noisy, you two suona have done it.
Am I a movie fan?
I know that the Mien are not allowed to enter the backstage.
Noisy, you two suona do have choked?
Don't go out and choke. Go to your place.
But, please, there is a heavenly suo-do.
It's a bite, it's a back-up Joe
I know, are you ready for the backstage?
Don't be quick, go out.
Noisy, you two are wearing the wrong clothes
Goo, beg you!
Someone's banging for nothing.
Catch them, and hold them up!
Oh, beggarly choke!
Quickly, I'm not sure, I'm not sure, I'm not sure, I'm not sure.
Come to my place, come to my place, damn it!
Hey, you want to stall the golden horse prize?
Do not add material to the noise at any time.
The unhappiness of the world.
Hustle, you go!
Come on, yo, let's get him in the back.
Quickly, carry him to the backstage.
Let me down! Let me go!
Noisy, let me down! I'm bawling!
Hey, baldy, I'm gagging.
clinch
Mom.
I'm not the only one. Hey, let me down.
Yes, don't stay.
Bawl.
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Well, I don't have my eyes open.
What a choke! What a choke!
Wow, the crowd is choking.
I have another chance to win a prize.
It's so choking! It's so choking!
Go out and continue to skip
Keep on dancing!
"The relationship is salty, the jumping, the pacing.
Lance, gimmick, Lance, Lance.
Thank you, yo. Thank you, yo.
Quickly, the curtain falls... Unh!
Chirp, even the lantern bridge is down.
Come on, yo, let's go up.
Right, right, right.
What are you doing?
I'll change my clothes soon.
Morning. - What? - Yeah.
C Va E Asahi S]!
According to the analysis of my computer.
I'm sorry.
It's two hearts smacking each other.
There's a bunch of mahjong left.
Do you know that the world is full of people who are fighting against each other?
That's why we're going to shoot the burglars.
The first line is MAP
Relationship Map
Bag
Exhort, when Shi Shui-sheng is dying?
Sung Il Keung Tun Nine Dragons Phen
So I'll show you a map of Kowloon Brown.
Second row P6, PD 6
Relationship with the sea
That's right!
So, the final line of sale of B3 has been choked to silence.
What? Unh!
You're not even a noise.
I'm looking for a throat, B3.
Bag of tricks!
Oh, you have a brain, Soo-ho.
Not as much as you.
Hey, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Drink.
No, I don't know how to swim, Joe.
I'm all right.
I'm with you.
So, what do you think?
You're a national traitor!
I got it.
I'll get you, I'll get you.
Don't give it back, it's a fake drink, what's the real deal?
Ah! Oh, my God.
Bald Head!
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm not guilty!
Oh, come on.
Have you come to do it again?
Do you want to be paid for my stall?
Come on, you're leaving.
White knuckle socks.
Then we won't have to show up.
Then you can call me if you need anything.
I'll bury a thousand horses and help you with your noise.
Come on, let's go.
The way to the more regular water salary I gradually
friends
Alberg, wear a shirt.
If you are lazy and kind, email me for smuggling, CHHECEK I will really
Hey, Mangalam!
White... - Oh, come on.
You've set up a network.
Tell me about the Un Un.
You can't leak the truth.
It's either you die or they die today.
Then what about you?
I'm not going to hold your two dots.
Un, a hundred hands, a hundred socks, a hundred yards, a hundred breaths.
It's more of a disaster than your death today.
No noise, need a howl for it
You're lucky to have a chance.
Then what about you?
Unh, I'll stay quiet for the big show.
Drought III
You'll get a lot of brown.
Oh, Jin, it's all over!
I don't want to call a thousand horses a gag.
What? Choke on a thousand cars and horses?
Call Montreal for the booth caller
I'm covering up.
Same as
But you've laid down a web of heaven and earth again.
I don't think so.
I Next
Ah, Theo, no, no. You want to die?
Wait for me to be silent. Wait for me to be called!
Whistle, hey, look at the Un, blindly listen.
Stop! Unh! Wait for me to devour!
Stop the Un, Stop the Un, Stop the Un, Pour the Un, Pour the Un
A surrender, he surrenders, he surrenders!
You don't have to use the noise.
I am like a car, but I have the advantage but not the reality.
What are you choking on?
♪ chirp, sing degree listen ♪
Howl of the Kisses
You're a ghost.
I can see so many stars
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What about the margins, the disgusting snap?
Do it already.
Donate!
friends
What? Choke? Well, oh?
The Universe of Heaven and Earth?
Ah, it's so good!
Look!
Wait for me to be silent.
Let's do it!
Ha ha ha, there's a leftover
I... come.
Mimi!
Ha, ha, you're awake again
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I have something to do.
You?
Help! I don't know how to swim.
What are you doing?
(b) the number of people who have been given the opportunity to work in the industry for a long time.
Hey, what are you doing in the morning?
Hey, where is he?
What are you doing? You don't have to choke on it.
Falling...
Let it go, let it go up
Officer Ham, let him go.
It's up to him, he's such a beer, and he's such a grandfather.
The best shot is to drive the car.
Well... Related.
Ha, ha, ha.
The man, the old dog, shouted that he was as mean as a bitch.
Hey, the pretty boy sucks.
"There's begging and choking. You and I are not demons.
"Wipe off the blame and sit down and talk"
"You need a hand, I'll give a hand.
"All the hardships are not worthwhile.
"You are at my side, I am no longer at a loss"
"A pair of rickets are strong.
"I am all for sale"
"You won't be surprised.
" Best File ヘルメンズ
"There's begging and choking. You and I are not demons.
"Wipe off the blame and sit down and talk"
"You need a hand, I'll give a hand.
"All the hardships are not worthwhile.
"You are at my side, I am no longer at a loss"
"A pair of rickets are strong.
"I am all for sale"
" You can have a safe trip
" Best File ヘルメンズ
"The Best of Our Land"
"Always the Best Shot"