junh1024
and artist team
CLAMP
present...
Extended
S
I'm Sakura, I'm just a girl-a,
and now I know that,
I found a magic world
Yes it's mystic,
I know it's magic,
and I can SEE, just what's in the cards for me
I know, it's true,
It's Me and Li – we're gonna fight for you, we'll
find the cards, catch them now,
be in charge, hold 'em now, wait...
So now catch me, catch you,
catch me cardcaptors!
Never be afraid of what's in the cards
Can you catch me, catch you, catch me
catch me cardcaptors?
Open doors, no never run away
'cuz you just can't be afraid of the cards!
THE • CARD • CAP • TORS!
Re-authored by junh1024
Many sources used
Special thanks to usotsuki on irc.hoshinet.org
[cards flapping]
It's... the dream!
One Fateful Day
[alarm ringing]
[gasp]
Um...
[yawn]
What a weird dream.
Sakura, hurry up or you're gonna be late!
Huh?
Coming!
This was the day that changed my life.
the day I discovered the Clow Book.
It started out like every other morning.
and as usual.
I was already late.
Morning'
Sakura. If you tried,
do you think you could be any louder?
I wasn't THAT loud.
You sounded like a small dinosaur up there.
I was walking normally!
Hey, I'm lucky.
How many guys get a dinosaur
for a little sister?
Stop calling me a dinosaur!
Pancakes, anyone?
Ah!
My dad found the Clow Book
at the university.
No one could open it.
but he said there was something
unusual about the book
that made him bring it home.
Here you go.
Smells great
That's my mom.
Even though she died
a long time ago.
I like to think she's
watching over me.
and I think she'd be proud.
Bye Dad.
Better hurry if you're gonna
catch up With Tori.
You staying late tonight?
Yeah, I got practice.
Have a good day!
I hope I can catch up with him...
Wow!
And this is how it all began.
[laughing]
Oh, good! There's Tori.
Tori, wait up!
Hey, relax!
What's the big hurry, squirt?
Nothing...
I hope he's riding with
us to school today
There he is.
Julian!
Uh, hey guys!
What's up?
Uh, not much...
Uh, hey Sakura.
You're sure early today.
Yeah.
Gee, I can't think of a reason why.
[Sakura groans]
You can ride to school with us anytime.
Sometimes I can't believe Julian
and my brother are friends.
They're nothing like each other.
Julian's always so nice to me.
And he's so cute!
Catch you later, Sakura.
Huh?
Oh
I wish I was in high school too.
So, have you come up With your
independent study topic yet?
No
I thought of the best idea.
I'm gonna make a documentary on
the life of the fourth-grade girl.
You are?
Madison always comes up with the
best ideas for independent study.
Last year her project
was the best in the class!
Oh yeah. And I need YOU
to be my fourth-grade girl.
Can I videotape you after school?
I guess so.
if you don't mind shooting
a video of drill team practice.
The ancient Egyptians
worshipped the sun god Ra.
Now Ra was considered
to be all-powerful.
and so the symbol chosen
to represent him...
I wonder where it came from.
I like your drawing, Sakura.
What is it?
You...mean this?
Sakura?
Continue reading.
'Kay.
Tell you later.
We're on line 48.
The sun god Ra was considered
so powerful that only very..."
[girls cheering]
That was a perfect backflip.
I know!
Everyone, grab your batons and practice.
[whistle]
I can't stop thinking about
that dream I had last night
Maybe I'll ask Madison about it
Huh?
[bonk]
Sakura may be the best baton
twirler our school has ever had.
Mm-hm.
But sometimes she's a real klutz.
Hi, I'm home!
Dad? Tori?
[rumbling]
Huh?
Hm.
Ah, pudding...
[rumbling]
Huh?
What's that noise?
It's coming from Dad's library!
[rumbling]
I wish Dad or Tori were here...
What if it's a burglar?
[rumbling]
[sigh]
I'll take a look inside.
If someone's there,
I'll call the police.
[rumbling]
[creaking]
[light switch]
[rumbling]
Ha!
There's no one there.
Huh?
Where's that glowing coming from?
[gasp]
The book in my dream!
Ah!
Huh?
They're cards.
"The Windy?" Hmm,
I wonder what it's for.
The Windy...
[gasp]
Ah!
[screaming]
[cards flapping]
[sigh]
What just happened?
Ah!
Hidey-howdy-howdy!
Thank you SO much for
waking me up little girl.
I have been stuffed in
that book for, like, ever.
What are you, some kind of squirrel?
Hey!
A toy? Where did the batteries...
I am NOT a toy!
I am Keroberos.
Guardian Beast of the Seal of the Clow Book!
You're a... Guardian Beast?
Yeah you got it, Sister!
You can call me Kero.
I keep the Clow cards
from getting into trouble, see?
[chuckle]
Huh? Waaah! No!
My Clow cards! Where are my cards?!
My precious cards...
Is this what you're looking for?
Huh?
Wow, the Windy card!
That's it! Thank you...
So, uh, where's the rest?
Well, as soon as I read the word "Windy"...
Yeah?
This huge wind started blowing...
Yeah yeah?
And they blew away.
Heh, heh. Blew away...
[Both laughing]
VVhat?
[groan]
There, I'm all finished!
See ya!
Where are you taking that?
Up to my room to eat.
Hey...
Ah, it's no use.
I don't know where the cards have gone.
I brought some pudding.
Oh, my favourite!
That book I was guarding
had Clow cards Inside it.
Clow cards?
Dangerous forces.
And now that the seal has been broken.
there's no telling what they'll do.
The Clow cards were created by a
very powerful magician named Clow Reed.
Each Clow card has its own
character and special powers.
They were designed to be free.
but the cards grew so strong and willful
that they couldn't be controlled.
So Clow Reed created a book
to keep the cards in.
and put a protective
seal on the cover.
They sound dangerous.
Mm-hm.
And that's why I gotta get them back.
AND you're gonna help me!
Huh?
Why do *I* have to?
Because YOU'RE the one
who summoned the Windy card
and set them free in the first place!
Yeah, but It was YOUR job to guard the seal
and make sure the Clow cards didn't escape.
I know... I just took a little nap.
For how long?
Thirty years or so.
I never said being a guardian was easy!
But if you were able to open the Clow Book's seal,
you must have very strong magical powers.
So uh, what's your name anyway?
Sakura.
Okay. Sakura, go stand over there.
Key to the Seal.
this girl will carry out the sacred promise.
Her name is Sakura.
I command you to bestow her
with your magical powers.
Release the power!
Ahh!
Sakura! Take the staff!
All right!
I, Keroberos, name Sakura
Cardcaptor!
This is crazy!
No way! I'm not doing it,
Ahh, that pudding hit the spot.
Listen! I can't be a cardcaptor!
Are you sure?
Umm, once you capture all
the cards, you'll be a hero.
Yeah, well, I'm just a kid.
I'm not old enough to
capture the cards yet.
Yeah well, you were old enough
to let the Clow cards loose
They'd still be in the book if you
hadn't taken a thirty-year nap!
[Kero groans]
[Sakura groans]
[strong wind blowing]
Where'd that come from?
Sakura!
Huh?
[screech]
What's that?
It's a Clow card!
Here?
It's the Fly card all right.
Well, don't just stand there!
Do something!
Like what?
Get out there and capture that Clow card!
What?
[breaking windows]
You could have at least let me change...
A true cardcaptor can battle in anything!
Even in pyjamas!
Man, I don't stand a chance against that thing.
You're a cardcaptor!
[screech]
Huh?
Sakura! Use your magic!
Just call on the Key
like I showed you before!
Mm-hm,
O Key of Clow.
the power of magic,
the power of light,
surrender the wand,
the force ignite!
Release!
Ready, Sakura?
[screech]
The Fly card has already
revealed its true form.
You should be able to use
the Windy card to capture it.
I don't know.
You'll just have to get
up close to it and...huh?
[both scream]
[screech]
I think it's after us!
Sakura, call the Windy card!
[screech]
Today would be good
Sakura, you gotta use the card now!
But it's chasing us'
Let's get outta here!
But you're the cardcaptor!
If you can't stop it, no one can!
But I don't know how!
Huh?
Wait, I got an idea.
Please, just hurry!
Sakura!
Be careful!
[screech]
Windy card.
form a chain and tie up
the Fly card's wings!
Windy!
[screech]
[The Fly screeching]
Clow card. I command you to
return to your power confined!
Fly card!
You did it, Sakura!
I didn't think I could.
Well, I did.
And that's why I chose ya, kid.
I TOLD you, that
can't be a cardcaptor!
Aww come on. You mean you're gonna
quit now just because it Isn't easy?
[Kero laughing]
Besides, you've captured the Fly card.
Touch your staff to it.
Why? What's gonna happen?
Just give It a try.
Wow!
So, how do you like flying?
It's the best!
I knew I could count on you,
Cardcaptor Sakura.
Yeah!
Wait a minute.
I haven't agreed to anything yet!
Kero was right.
He could count on me.
And from that day on, my life
would never be the same.
Supervising Director
Morio Asaka
Supervising
Production Coordinator
Nanase Okawa
(CLAMP)
Character Designer
Kumiko Takahashi
Costume & card Designer
Mokona Apapa
(CLAMP)
Background Designer
Katsufumi Hariu
What's all the fuss about?
No need to scream and shout,
Director of Cameras
Hisao Shirai
Director of Animation
Kumiko Takahashi
Producer of Animation
Tetsuya Ono
(MAD HOUSE)
Producer
Eizo Kondo
(SOGO VISION)
I'm just gonna sit and chill out
Executive Producers
Yasuko Uchizawa (NHK)
Akira Watanabe (NEP21)
When it comes at you,
What you gonna do?
Animation Studio
Mad House
Color Stylist
Madoka Katsunuma
Just take it in, oh
It's all groovy!
Directors
Morio Asaka
Sunao Katabuchi
Mamoru Kanbe
Kazunori Mizuno
Shoji Yabushita
Ken Ando
Akira Mano
Yorimichi Nakano
Nabuaki Nakanishi
Akio Sakai
Jun-ichi Sakata
Masaru Kitao
Hitoyuki Matsui
You can be happy now,
Don't have to stress you out,
Script Editor
Tatsuhiko Urahata
Writers
Nanase Okawa
Hiroshi Ishii
Jiro Kaneko
Tomoko Ogawa
Tomoyasu Okubo
You just gotta let it ride
Gonna pass on through,
No matter what you do, so let go!
ENGLISH LANGUAGE VERSION
Executive Producers
Michael Hirsh
Patrick Loubert
Toper Taylor
Supervising Producers
Jocelyn Hamilton
Stephen Hodgins
Line Producer
Tina Karski
Associate Producer
Jim Weatherford
Post Production Supervisor
Keith A. Goddard
Production Coordinator
Diana Gage
Voice Director
Karl Willems
Let it fly away... far away!
WITH THE VOICE TALENTS OF
Sakura
Kero
Li
Madison
Tori
Julian
Aiden
Carly McKillip
Matt Hill
Rhys Huber
Maggie Blue O'Hara
Tony Sampson
Sam Vincent
Brian Drummond
English Script Adaptation
Jennifer Pertsch
Post Production
Jason Held
Picture Editor
Doug Appeldoom
Re-Recording Mixer
Keith A. Goddard
Recording Engineers
Trevor Smith
Michael Iske
Assistant
Recording Engineer
Aaron Macdonald
Madness lasts for so long,
How it happens to ya,
Dialogue Editors
James Corrigall
Angello Floresco
Christopher Cleator
Additional Sound Effects
Luke Martin
Me know how it gets ya – so easy I know?
Music
Jack Lenz
for Downright Adagio Inc.
Music Editors
Peter Branton
Anthony Crea
Daniel Fernandez
Simon Berry
Don't 'cha let it tease ya
Soon as you refuse it
English Version
Produced In Association With
The Ocean Group
Vancouver, Canada
Won't know how to get 'cha and then it will go
'cuz it's all, GROOVY!
Welcome cardcaptor fans!
I'm everyone's favourite host, Kero.
tellin' ya like it is!
In today's episode,
Sakura remembered the day
she discovered the Clow Book.
and met me.
Sakura's a real pro
on the inline skates.
Notice the protective
yet stylish padding.
This year, all of the children
at Reedington Elementary
are sporting this charming uniform.
a classic sailor to with a crisp
white tie and pleated skirt
But Sakura is a real trend-setter.
and always accessorises her outfits
with her special winged symbol.
Pretty snappy, huh? HUH?
And a pair of black-buckled
shoes with white socks
makes the outfit complete.
This reporter's seen some
pretty funky battle costumes.
but even I've never seen anyone capture
a card in their pyjamas before.
Sakura's definitely got what it takes.
See you later!