Ruri,
I... I...
I can't go out with you!
I like someone else!
Onee-chan!
What is it, Tama-chan?
Onii-chan hasn't been visiting us lately.
Y-Yeah, that's true!
Did Onee-chan and him have a fight?
Well, who knows?
Will he come celebrate Christmas with us?
I guess I lose!
I ought to congratulate you!
You are the only person who could admit such a thing.
Kuroneko...
You no longer have the right to exist amongst the darkness.
Take that holy sword of yours and go save the world.
You, who shattered my first love, should have no difficulty doing so.
Go on a date with Senpai
Tell Senpai more about me
Invite Senpai to my house
This is what you wanted, right?
Kuroneko...
Yes, from the very beginning...
This...
This was our fate...
I knew that...
AV Editing: junh1024, Subs: Doki